foreign
[Music]
ER this year it means that I am
competing with so many brilliant people
who are doing so much good work in the
digital social media space
and coming up for the corporate HR five
years ago and stepping into a brand new
industry the financial industry I must
say that social media has helped me so
much in branding myself and accelerated
myself in this career role and being a
winner for this award means that I've
probably done something right in 2021
and I hope that in 2022 all of us will
work harder to create greater public
offenders to help protect people and
make better financial decisions thank
you everyone and I wish everybody to
have a very good year in 2022
thank you